http://www.hilmersonrv.com/read-our-privacy-statement--privacy-policy

Hilmerson RV
Privacy Policy
ONLINE PARTS PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY:
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.
SECURITY POLICY
Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.
REFUND POLICY
We offer 30 Day Money Back Guarantee on almost every product we offer. No returns on special order items or Electrical items. All returns must be in original packaging and 100% re-sellable condition. Please call our parts department at 320-632-4065. All freight charges will be paid by customer. All refunds will be provided as a credit to the credit card used at the time of purchase within five (5) business days upon receipt of the returned merchandise.
SHIPPING POLICY
Please be assured that your items will ship out within two days of purchase. Our online parts center will determine all shipping charges. The carriers that may be used are: U.S. Postal Service (USPS), United Parcel Service (UPS) or FedEx. Sorry but we cannot ship to P.O. Boxes.
Credit card authorization and verification must be received prior to processing.
Federal Express and UPS deliveries occur Monday through Friday, excluding holidays.
If you require express or 2 day shipping, please call us at 320.632.4065 for charges.
PLEASE NOTE: Out of state orders WILL NOT be charged sales tax. In state orders will be charged 6.875% sales tax.
RENTALS PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY:
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.
SECURITY POLICY
Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.
REFUND POLICY
No rental reservation refunds given. In the event of a cancelation, the entire rental reservation will be lost no matter what time frame is given.
SALES PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY:
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect
personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically
receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including
your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell
your personally identifiable information to anyone.
SECURITY POLICY
Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets
Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software
available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal
information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot
be read over the internet.
REFUND POLICY
Customer deposits received via the internet towards the purchase of any type of vehicle Hilmerson RV and Marine sells only will be refunded thru management. Please call Bryan Hilmerson at 320-632-4065 to resolve any issue you may have.
×
×
×
×
